Guide to the Intersession Program on Women records, 1969
Intersession Program on Women records, 1969
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Intersession Program on Women records, 1969.
23-2-1238
.3 cubic ft.
Transcripts, correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Transcripts of taped sessions of a conference on "Women Today" sponsored by the New York State College of Human Ecology (then the College of Home Economics), including transcript of a session on "The Black Woman in America"; memoranda; correspondence; schedules; agenda; and summaries and commentary on sessions.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Transcripts of taped sessions of a conference on "Women Today" sponsored by the New York State College of Human Ecology (then the College of Home Economics), including transcript of a session on "The Black Woman in America"; memoranda; correspondence; schedules; agenda; and summaries and commentary on sessions.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; New York State College of Home Economics.
Subjects:
African American women.; Feminism.; Minority women.; Women--Political activity.; Women--Social conditions.; Women's rights.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Memos to Participants and Organizers, Meeting Minutes, Agenda Revisions, May 1968- January 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- News Paper Clippings and Press Releases, May 1968- January 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Panel Discussion: "How Men Look at Women and How Women Look at Themselves", January 22, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Panel Discussion: "Is the 'Question of Women' a Political Question?", January 22, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Panel Discussion, January 22, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Panel Discussion on the Education of Women, January 23, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Panel Discussion: "Child Bearing, Child Rearing, Abortion, and Contraception", January 23, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Panel Discussion: "The Future of Women in America", January 23, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Panel Discussion: "The Psychological Difference Between Men and Women", January 24, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Panel Discussion: "The Black Woman in America", January 25, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wrap-Up by Sheila Tobias, Conference Coordinator, January 25, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)